Tim Westberg

Lake Elsinore, CA, 92532 **Phone**: (951) 852-2584

Email: <u>TimWestberg@formulagen.com</u> **GitHub**: <u>https://github.com/Timwestberg</u>

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/tim-westberg-516022162/

Portfolio: https://timwestberg.herokuapp.com

Personal bio and objective

I am a user-focused Web Developer with a passion for integrating technologies to solve problems and improve existing methods. My background in sales, finance, and office management provides me with a unique perspective on how end-users interact with websites and software platforms. I enjoy approaching programming challenges from different angles and collaborating with others to create meaningful web applications that effectively elevate the user and client experience. My ultimate goal is to provide solutions that are simple and intuitive to clients.

Education

Computer Science, Bachelor of Science (B.S.) in Progress, *August 2017 – Present* Mira Costa Community College, Carlsbad, California

Full Stack Development and MERN Stack Certification, *August 2018 – January 2019* University of California San Diego

High School Diploma, 2010-2014

Vista Murrieta High School, Murrieta, CA

Cumulative GPA: 3.85

Experience

Oscar Campana (O.C.) Interpreting Agency Carlsbad, CA, July 2017 – Present

Application developer and Administrative assistant

Application developer

- Designed custom web application for booking appointments.
- Store client, contractor and appointment information.
- Assist staff with finding nearby interpreters relevant to the appointment location, accomplished by integrating Google Maps and React.Js.
- Create a comfortable and simple UI experience.

Administrative Assistant

- Manage company emails and employee training.
- Process confidential client information.
- QuickBooks manager.

Life Insurance Agent and Hiring Assistant Manager

- Hiring and interviewing potential job candidates.
- Excelled at sales and provided excellent customer service
- Gained interpersonal experience and extensive leadership training
- Working in a team-oriented environment

Twest Financial, Lake Elsinore, CA, 2010 – 2016 (QuickBooks)

Bookkeeper

- Entering transactions
- Class tracking
- Bank reconciliation
- Invoicing

I am proficient in and have experience with:

- React.js
- Express
- Node.js
- Mongoose
- MongoDB
- MySQL
- Material Design
- Material CSS
- Axios

- Passport.js
- JavaScript,
- JQUERY
- Node.js,
- HTML
- CSS
- Quick Books Enterprise and lower, Quick Books Point of Sale
- Typing: 75 words per minute